[♪ theme music playing]
WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, ETC. ARE FICTIONAL
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED
WITH GUARDIANS PRESENT
ANIMALS WERE FILMED
UNDER EXPERT SUPERVISION AND WELFARE RULES
[dish clinks]
[inhales deeply]
[exhales]
Oh, I wonder if she even had dinner.
But what brings Mr. Kim
all the way over here?
[♪ upbeat dreamy music playing]
Mom, take this.
-What's the rush?
-Take this.
Come here, Sundol.
What is it?
Are you going somewhere?
Yeah, I'm heading out to meet someone.
Who?
Well, Mr. Kim.
Mr. Kim?
[gasps]
That Mr. Kim?
-Have dinner without me.
-Okay.
What brings Mr. Kim here?
Meri!
Gosh, is something wrong?
Let's see.
MERI
[chuckles softly]
[♪ gentle, pleasant music playing]
Take your time.
[giggles]
It's okay if she doesn't come home.
[singing]
♪ Amor fati ♪
[humming]
After my parents were transferred
to the hospital,
they passed away the next day.
[♪ soft, melancholy music playing]
You mean...
Your dad was in the accident...
because he turned around to talk to you?
[Grandpa] What was that?
[Philnyun] Honey.
[Kim Wooju] After that,
Grandpa never saw me again.
[Grandpa grunts]
[Kim Wooju] He said just seeing me
made him angry.
He had a hard time accepting
that his son and daughter-in-law died
because of his grandson.
Wooju, this is it.
Let's get out.
[children chattering]
[♪ soft, melancholy music continues]
[Kim Wooju] After that,
I began my studies abroad.
Since then, I learned
how to live on my own.
You never came back
to Korea all that time?
I did. I came to see you.
When?
It was back in middle school
during the summer break.
I asked around
through the detective in charge
and went all the way to Yeosu to see you.
[♪ poignant music playing]
[Youngsook] Would that family
appreciate it
when the couple's already dead?
Your dad ended up dead for being nosy.
If only he hadn't gone
to the police station.
[sighs wearily]
PREMIUM ORANGE JUICE GIFT SET
Oh, I remember that.
The drinks were in front of our house
on my dad's death anniversary.
[gasps]
PREMIUM ORANGE JUICE GIFT SET
I'M SORRY
So, that was you, Wooju.
But you were hasty.
You should've heard Mom out until the end.
Dad's accident happened because of them.
Yes, I know.
You know your dad's always been nosy.
It was in his nature
to pry into other people's business.
But it feels sad
[clicks tongue]
that they also ended up dead
even though he stepped up.
[sighs regretfully]
I was hasty.
[chuckles softly]
I should've stayed to hear her out.
So, don't dwell on it anymore.
Okay.
What's life been like for you?
Well...
I lived well with Mom and Sori.
Then, whenever I missed my dad,
I came here.
When I was little,
I used to travel a lot in my dad's taxi.
In spring, we'd go to Seomjingang River
to see the plum blossoms.
In the fall, we'd go to Naejangsan
Mountain to see the autumn leaves.
And we came here often, too.
[♪ gentle, poignant music playing]
Dad!
Dad?
Dad, where are you?
[crying] Dad!
Dad!
Dad.
Dad, where are you?
Daddy is right here!
[chuckling]
[Meri] One day, when I was little,
the sun set while I was drawing,
and Dad disappeared.
What a crybaby.
I didn't know exactly where I was,
so I was terrified all alone.
Then he suddenly appeared,
lifting me up to his shoulders.
And like magic, I was no longer scared.
You know how life
sometimes just feels dark and hopeless.
I walk here
every time my life feels like that.
You see that?
The star that's shining
the brightest over there.
Yes.
I feel like that's my dad.
I feel like he became a star
so that whenever I feel lost,
he can light my path like a lighthouse.
[sighs contentedly]
Ms. Yoo.
Can I just say one thing?
That thing
is a satellite.
[♪ whimsical sting]
[chuckles sheepishly]
They say the big, bright light
is actually a satellite.
But I can be your lighthouse.
I'll stand right beside you.
How?
[hums thoughtfully]
-What?
-Come on, hop on.
[Meri chuckles nervously]
Gosh.
[♪ enthralling orchestral music playing]
How is it? Can you see well?
I can, but...
-I'm heavy, aren't I?
-Not at all.
-You're light as a feather.
-[chuckles softly]
Still, it's okay now. You can put me down.
No, it's fine.
From now on,
I'll always be by your side
so you don't get scared...
-[twig snaps]
-[Kim Wooju exclaims]
-[thuds]
-[groans]
[chuckling]
A stone...
Why is there a stone here? Jeez...
[chuckles softly]
[grunts, sighs]
-[Kim Wooju gasps in awe]
-[Meri] So pretty.
[Kim Wooju] There are so many of them.
[exclaims]
Here, rest on my arm.
[♪ upbeat dreamy music playing]
[sighs contentedly]
WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
EPISODE 8
[indistinct chatter]
[footsteps on stairs]
[Jingyeong] Wooju, wait.
[♪ soft, melancholy music playing]
Am I the one in the wrong here?
I find it ridiculous
that Meri dragged you into this,
and honestly, I don't get
why you're letting her string you along.
What you're feeling toward her
is just guilt, not love.
You got it wrong.
I like Meri.
So, don't assume you know how I feel.
If you're like this again,
I'll really get mad.
[sniffles]
I like you, Wooju.
Everyone else knows.
So, why don't you?
[crying softly]
[panting]
What are you doing there?
[sighs softly]
Ms. Yoon.
[sniffles, breath trembling]
[sniffles]
What are you doing here, Mr. Baek?
There's no running today.
I run every day.
And I normally take a break here.
You're in my spot.
[♪ poignant, melancholy music playing]
[Jingyeong sighs]
Why are you sighing?
It's not like you.
Am I not allowed to sigh?
Why? Because I was born on the third base?
Did you take it to heart?
Yes.
And that I'm not attractive as a woman.
I took it deep into my heart.
I'm joking.
You look so serious.
I'm always serious.
[chuckles softly]
Have you told him?
Pardon?
To the person you've liked
since you were kids.
It looks like you've confessed.
This isn't something
you should be embarrassed about.
If you hadn't done anything,
you would've regretted it someday.
If you can't stop thinking about it,
you can run with me.
[Jingyeong sighs wearily]
[sighs]
That's why he helped you out.
Because he felt bad.
He wanted to pay you back.
What you're feeling toward her
is just guilt, not love.
[♪ poignant, melancholy music continues]
[panting softly]
[panting]
I messed up.
I messed up everything.
[breathing heavily]
I...
actually knew it all along.
[breath trembling]
That the person I like...
has someone else in his heart.
So, I got in the way, childishly.
[breath trembling]
But it just made things worse.
[crying]
What was I thinking?
Why did I do that?
[sobbing]
[sighs]
[Jingyeong continues sobbing]
[dog barking]
-[exclaims]
-[chuckles softly]
This is Meri's sister's room.
You should sleep here.
Oh, sure.
Oh, and this.
-Gosh, here.
-Thank you.
These are all washed clean.
Thank you.
By the way, you can speak comfortably.
[exclaiming]
Oh, okay then.
You must be tired. Have some rest.
Okay, good night.
Sure. Good night to you, too.
[chuckles softly]
[clears throat]
[sighs in relief]
[whispers] Hey, Meri.
[softly] Hey, what brought him here?
What?
I don't know. Let's talk about it later.
[in neutral tone]
Is he here to see you?
Gosh, I said, let's talk about it later.
Sleep tight.
[hesitates] You brat.
Oh, goodness.
There's definitely something
going on between them.
[whispers] There definitely is.
[taps bottle]
[bottle clinks on table]
[grunts softly]
[phone vibrates]
TEAM LEADER KIM WOOJU
[Kim Wooju] Are you asleep?
[Meri] No, I was just getting into bed.
Are you having trouble sleeping?
[Kim Wooju] Yes,
can you come to my room now?
[Meri] Now?
[♪ whimsical music playing]
[gasps]
It's a bit awkward with Mom here.
[♪ ethereal sparkle]
[♪ enthralling, whimsical music playing]
[♪ whimsical sting]
[exclaims quizzically]
Is this why you asked me to come?
It doesn't seem to be afraid of humans.
I mean...
Why isn't it flying away?
[♪ gripping, whimsical music playing]
[Kim Wooju exclaims quizzically]
[chirping]
[exclaims]
[insect continues chirping]
[Kim Wooju exclaims in awe]
It doesn't even bite.
Ms. Yoo.
[sighing in relief]
You're so reliable.
Oh, this isn't a big deal.
You're totally my ideal type.
[chuckles]
Is your type someone
who's good at catching bugs?
Yes.
[both chuckle softly]
Then I'll catch them every day for you.
[giggles]
[knock at door]
[Youngsook] Are you asleep?
[knocks at door]
-[whispers] She left, right?
-[softly] No, she hasn't.
[♪ whimsical music playing]
[whispers] I think I heard the door close.
[softly] Gosh, she hasn't left yet.
She has.
[Kim Wooju exclaims]
See? She left.
When did she leave?
[♪ upbeat whimsical music playing]
[both laughing]
[Meri whispers] The walls are paper-thin.
We'll wake her up.
[Kim Wooju softly] Okay, I'll be quiet.
You stay still, Meri.
[Meri softly] I didn't move!
[Kim Wooju shushes]
SUNDOL'S HOUSE
They're all ripe.
Sundol.
Oh, dear.
[Sundol panting]
[sighs contentedly]
[sighs, sniffles]
[♪ whimsical music playing]
[chuckles softly]
[footsteps approaching]
[gasps]
Good morning.
Good morning. Did you sleep well?
Yes.
Go and wash up so we can eat.
-Okay.
-Good.
Here.
-It's hot.
-[exclaims excitedly]
Well, then.
Eat up.
Who eats samgyetang in the morning?
What's wrong with it?
You've got no problem
eating pork belly for breakfast.
But Mr. Kim probably
doesn't normally eat breakfast.
No, it's good to have a hearty breakfast.
Thank you for the food.
[hums in satisfaction]
-It's delicious.
-[chuckles softly]
This isn't just any chicken.
Do you know Korean hen?
Of course, I do.
It's a chicken you serve
when the son-in-law visits.
[chuckling] That's right.
[chuckles nervously]
What do you mean, son-in-law?
Where did you even get this Korean hen?
What do you mean, where?
I went to Mija's early this morning
and begged her for it
in exchange for beef.
It tastes even better
because it's valuable.
Here.
Try it with this.
It's freshly made,
so it's really delicious.
[hums in satisfaction]
By the way, can I ask you something?
Of course.
You know that Meri was married once.
[acknowledges]
-I do.
-[Youngsook chuckles softly]
They say young people these days
have weddings
but don't register their marriage.
But she registered her marriage first
because of me.
[♪ gentle, poignant music playing]
I told her that
I wouldn't help her with the house
unless they registered their marriage.
It was because she was getting older,
but they kept postponing the wedding.
[chuckles softly]
I didn't know my actions would make
my daughter a divorcée.
I told you, it's not your fault.
It is.
It's my fault that she became a divorcée.
It's because I pushed her into it.
So, if you want to blame someone,
blame me, okay?
No, ma'am.
Such things aren't important to me.
But your family
should also be okay with it.
Mom.
Stop going overboard.
I'm not.
You guys were
tightly hugging each other all night.
[♪ dramatic sting]
[Kim Wooju mumbles]
Girl, I'm pretty sharp.
[clears throat]
Anyway, if your family mistreats my Meri,
I won't let her marry you.
I can't let her live like that.
Even if it's just for a day, [taps table]
she should live feeling loved.
Okay, ma'am.
But actually, I don't have any parents.
I only have my grandmother.
And she really sees people
for who they are,
so don't worry.
That's a relief.
I also don't expect anything
from the man who'll marry my daughter.
I'll be happy if he's healthy
and all is well
as long as Meri is cherished.
That's what I'm very good at.
[♪ upbeat, whimsical music playing]
Good. [chuckles]
Oh, here.
Eat mine, too.
You need to fatten up.
I'll try to fatten up nicely.
[chuckles softly]
[hums in satisfaction]
[exclaims contentedly]
It's so good.
-Mom, you should eat, too.
-Okay.
-[Youngsook whispers] Eat up.
-[chuckles softly]
[Youngsook chuckling]
My name is Kim Wooju,
and I owe my life to your help, sir.
YOO JAEMAN
I'm sorry it took me so long
to come and greet you.
BORN IN 1968
DIED IN 2000
Thank you for what you did.
[♪ gentle, melancholy music playing]
Honey, the boy you saved
grew up to be such a gentleman.
You did something really big
before you passed away.
You saved a man
who'll be with Meri before leaving.
[Youngsook giggles]
You practically brought them together.
[chuckling]
[phone vibrating]
It's Sori.
She must've called
since it's Dad's anniversary.
-It's my sister.
-I see.
Hey.
[Sori in English] Hi, sister.
[in Korean] Where's Mom?
My youngest.
Have you been well?
What time is it in the US?
It's a bit past ten.
We just finished,
so we're cleaning up the hall.
I'm here at the columbarium
with your sister.
Say hello.
Gosh, I wanted to go for the anniversary,
but it was hard to get time off.
[in English] Sori, see you tomorrow.
[in English] See you tomorrow.
[in Korean] Just wait a little.
Once our restaurant closes,
I'll come right away.
[Meri] It's closing?
Why? You said the business was good.
How should I know?
It's up to my boss.
Anyway, I'll come back to Korea soon,
so I'll see you there.
By the way,
are you there alone?
Did Wooju not come again?
[hesitates]
Gosh, of course, he's here.
Here he is.
Look.
Hello.
Who's that?
[Youngsook] What do you mean?
It's Wooju, Kim Wooju.
Oh, my.
Did you change your face through surgery?
Oh, actually,
this Wooju is not that Wooju.
Look again.
He's a completely different person.
-They just share the same name.
-What?
What are you talking about?
-What happened is--
-Hey.
We'll talk about it when you get here.
Stay healthy. I'm hanging up now.
-[line disconnects]
-Why did you hang up?
She and Wooju should've talked more.
They can talk more later.
What's the hurry?
-Let's go now.
-Should we?
Okay.
We'll come again.
YOUNGSOOK'S RESTAURANT
Before you get going, take these with you.
This one here is our signature.
Seasoned dried pollack.
And this is bellflower root,
seasoned this morning.
Oh, I got this spicy marinated crab
from the next door...
That's enough.
I can't eat them all.
It's not just for you.
It's for both of you.
-Thank you so much.
-[Youngsook] Oh, my. Wait a minute.
What else should I give you?
Meri, get me a few containers
from that cabinet over there.
Let's see.
[creaking]
Oh, gosh...
You need a new cabinet.
You'll hurt yourself if these fall.
They're still good.
[Kim Wooju clears throat]
How many do you need?
Let's see...
Well...
Take out many.
[♪ whimsical music playing]
Oh, I need to go
to the bathroom for a second.
Take all of them out from the top.
Okay, then.
[Meri clears throat]
[clearing throat]
My mom's a bit much, isn't she?
[chuckles softly]
-She must like you a lot.
-[chuckles softly]
That's a relief.
Oh, I haven't told Mom
that you're the grandson
of Myungsoondang's CEO.
She's already worried
that your family might dislike me.
So, I thought that might shock her.
[chuckles softly]
We can tell her later.
When I first heard it from Jingyeong,
my mind totally went blank.
But things are a bit clearer now.
I think...
I'm going to tell Mr. Baek everything.
If the winning gets canceled,
I'm not sure what will happen.
It might end with me
just returning the house.
But in the worst case,
I could be sued.
Will you be okay?
When I was abandoned with just the debt,
I felt really lost.
At the time, I thought
that house was my last resort.
But now, I have something more important.
I want to stand tall in front of you.
And in front of those around you.
[♪ gentle, poignant music playing]
You see,
I'm going to work hard
and pay off my debt.
I know it's shameless for me to ask,
but could you wait for me a bit?
[♪ gentle music playing]
Whatever you decide,
I'll be right beside you.
Thank you for making
such a difficult decision.
No, I should thank you.
You gave me courage.
[Miyeon sighs] I told you
to take Eungsoo with you.
They'll probably need someone
at a director level for the US branch.
It would've been nice if he could've gone
to get a sense of things there.
Why? Did Eungsoo ask
to be sent to the US branch?
He's not the type to ask.
He's too soft to have ambition.
That's why you need
to take care of him more.
Lately, he has been learning English
from a private tutor.
It's the speaking
that he has a problem with.
His listening skills are okay.
That's not enough for the director level.
What if Wooju beats him again?
I'll take more care of Eungsoo, okay?
[clicks tongue] Okay.
When are you returning this time?
Since next week is
the 80th anniversary ceremony,
I'll be back before then.
[sighs wearily]
I'm so sick
of your business trips to the US.
How many times a year do you have to go?
I'll be back.
Eungsoo!
Drive your dad to the airport!
Okay.
[sighs] I'm really okay.
The driver will be here soon.
[hums uncertainly]
We only have a son.
You might as well make use of him.
Don't you think so?
Right.
Be quick, Eungsoo.
Okay.
-Let's go, Dad.
-Okay.
-I'm off.
About the plant in the US.
If it's in the final stages,
I guess your business trips
will lessen now.
It's only the beginning. [sighs]
We've got to do the equipment test runs
before the first batch comes out,
there's an OSHA audit coming up,
and we need to stabilize the lines, too.
[sighs wearily] In the end,
I have to be there.
I see.
When you're in the US,
please call Mom more often.
She worries a lot
when she can't reach you.
[chuckles softly]
No news is good news.
I get caught up with work,
and the time difference
makes it hard to call. [chuckles softly]
[phone vibrates]
[mistress] Are you free to call?
[♪ gripping, tense music playing]
[Hangu] I'm with Eungsoo right now.
[mistress] What time's your flight?
[Hangu] Three o'clock.
I'll call you when I get there.
You know, Mom really likes
the fig cookies from the duty-free shop.
And there's a new pair of shoes
from M Kors' SS line.
They'd make great gifts for Mom
since it's your wedding anniversary soon.
You know her shoe size, right?
What?
Mom's shoe size.
Oh, what was it?
It's 240mm.
Okay, thanks.
[grunts softly]
Bye, then.
Dad?
Have a safe trip.
Don't stay away for too long
since Mom's waiting.
[♪ unsettling, tense music playing]
[sighs nervously]
[engages handbrake]
We're here.
Why are we here?
[chuckles softly]
[gasps in awe]
These days,
they make the window frames slimmer.
It shows off the view perfectly.
Gosh, we need to renovate our house, too.
We don't have money for that.
Wooju is also unemployed now.
Seriously, Mom!
Why did you have to get ahead of yourself?
He quit his job for nothing
because of you.
How was I supposed to know
this would happen?
[sighing wistfully]
Only if Wooju could soften Jenny's heart
and make things work again.
Just like me, he's too full of pride.
Stop dreaming.
Jenny is in the past now.
Wooju wants Meri now, not Jenny.
Didn't you see him crying
because he missed Meri?
Meri?
Don't even mention her.
It makes my blood pressure spike.
-The name is now forbidden, okay?
-Fine.
-[whispers] Meri.
-Oh, you!
-That Meri...
-Wait for me!
Ms. Chun.
-Hurry up.
-What now?
[♪ gripping, whimsical music playing]
This place is...
-Is it your first time here?
-Yes.
Your mother's kitchen
looked a little outdated.
I think it'd be nice to redo it for her.
I see.
I was thinking about it, too.
I want to do it for her,
so could you help me?
No, you don't have to.
-I'll do it for her later--
-Ms. Yoo.
Please let me do this for her.
[chuckles softly, inhales deeply]
Now then, how about
something sleek and seamless,
matched to your mom's height?
Anything would do.
[exclaims in amazement]
[Meri] This one's very spacious.
[gasps]
[♪ gripping, comical music playing]
What are you doing?
[shushes]
Oh, my.
Is that Meri?
-[softly] Keep it down.
-[mouthing] Oh, right.
I think it is.
Who's that man?
[Wooju's sister] I don't know.
But he looks familiar.
[Eunsook] Who was it?
Since you're here, I'll see myself out.
My apologies.
[gasps] Oh, my gosh.
I can't believe this.
That man... You know.
[camera shutter clicks]
[grunts softly]
[beeps]
[phone vibrates]
[Wooju's sister] Isn't this the man
who was in your hospital room?
There's definitely something going on
between him and Meri.
[huffs]
[scoffs]
She said he was just
the client's team leader.
[♪ gripping, dramatic music playing]
No doubt he's the one who called Meri out
using his position as the client.
Where does he work?
[line ringing]
24 HOURS
WOMEN-ONLY SAUNA
[phone vibrating]
KIM WOOJU, DO NOT ANSWER
My gosh.
I almost answered.
Good thing I didn't delete his number.
[line ringing]
[automated voice] The call cannot
be connected. Transferring to voicemail.
[line disconnects]
Geez.
I need to know where he works
to send them an anonymous tip and ruin...
[Wooju] I can't get a hold of Meri.
Do you know where she is right now?
Oh, we had a small argument.
You know. Just a lovers' quarrel.
[Songhee acknowledges]
She's out on business right now,
so she might be hard to reach.
There's been an incident at Myungsoondang.
It's one of our clients.
She's probably
with the team leader from there.
Myungsoondang.
MYUNGSOONDANG
[scoffs]
[line ringing]
Oh, Mr. Kim Wooju?
He took a day off,
so he's not in the office today.
Yes, he is our team leader.
May I have your name, please?
[Philnyun] Myungsoondang's spirit
of giving back to society
began with our founder, my mother-in-law.
Right after the Korean War,
it all began as a small bakery
using just two sacks of flour
given by the US soldiers.
And my mother-in-law would never sell
the steamed buns she made for the poor,
even if a wealthy family offered
triple the price.
Although we live in an age
full of tricks and deceit,
Myungsoondang stands where it does today
because of our belief
in creating honest, wholesome food.
Thank you for taking the time
for this interview.
No, thank you.
[chuckles softly]
Our 80th anniversary ceremony
is coming up soon.
Please come by and have a meal.
Okay.
Bye, then.
You must be tired.
You should go inside and rest.
I'm okay.
Since we're out,
let's check out the garden.
[Miyeon] Mom!
[♪ dramatic, whimsical music playing]
[panting]
Mom, I'm here.
Hi, Ms. Kim.
Gosh, Mom.
Why are you working
in the garden in this heat?
Mom, take a seat here.
Mom.
Should I apply some of this for you?
If you have something to say,
spit it out already.
Oh, it's nothing.
It's just that people kept asking me.
Ask what?
It's the 80th anniversary soon.
So, whether you'll be announcing
your successor at the ceremony
is what everyone's been wondering.
You're the one who's curious.
Of course, I'm curious
since my Eungsoo is also in the line.
I'll leave it to someone qualified,
so stay out of it.
How can I stay out of it
when the playing field's tilted?
Since I was little,
you've always favored my brother
and treated me like an afterthought.
That same pattern's been passed down
to Wooju and Eungsoo.
How could I not feel uneasy?
When did I ever treat you
like an afterthought?
You always praised my brother
and didn't trust me with anything.
Our household was sexist,
and its preference for sons
was really strong.
You have no right to say that.
It wasn't sexism.
You received horrible grades.
Your tuition fee cost us more.
You had no perseverance,
so you'd always quit halfway.
And you are so gullible.
So, how could I trust you?
It's not my fault that I'm not so smart.
You're partly to blame
for my double-digit IQ, Mom.
It's all part of the genetics.
That's why I don't scold Eungsoo
for not being book smart.
I just say it's my fault.
Oh, my.
Sure, it's all my fault.
I'm sorry. Happy, now?
Where are you going, Mom?
I'm heading in because I can't stand you.
I have a headache now.
-[mutters angrily]
-What do you think you're doing?
[♪ dramatic, tense music playing]
Mom,
your perfectly fine head gets a headache
every time we talk, doesn't it?
You never listen until the end
and always dismiss me.
Fine.
I'm okay with you treating me that way.
But if you're like that
to my husband and my son,
I won't stand it.
I'm not all talk.
I'll make you regret how you mistreated
my husband and my son.
Just watch me.
[breath trembling, crying]
Miyeon!
[sighs wearily]
[phone vibrating]
WIFE
[sighs wearily]
[phone continues vibrating]
[mumbles]
[phone clatters]
What about Henry?
He's asleep.
He's out cold after his ice hockey lesson.
I know it's a bit early for the champagne,
but a single sip won't hurt
since we're so close to the end.
Still, don't let your guard down.
You know what Chairwoman Ko is like
since you've worked under her before.
All right.
I've waited this far.
I can hang on a little longer.
[glasses clink]
[hums in satisfaction]
This is nice.
Oh, right.
I had J Consulting dissolved
and wiped out all traces.
And I transferred the money
to your Swiss account.
Good work.
You haven't lost your touch.
[chuckles softly]
Anyway, you said Ms. Kim
is looking into J Consulting.
Do you think
they realized it's tied
to the private equity fund?
If so, it wouldn't be so peaceful still.
Even if they did, it's too late now.
There's nothing they can do.
[hums thoughtfully]
I can't wait to see
Chairwoman Ko's reaction.
If she found out the private equity fund
that financed the US plant was yours,
what face do you think she'd pull?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
The son-in-law she bossed around
like a servant
is the one holding her reins now.
[chuckles]
But for me,
I'm more curious about Miyeon's reaction.
Why her?
That woman invested
her father's inheritance
in a Hawaii hotel
and lost every penny of it.
If she finds out that was your doing...
[gasps]
At this rate, that family might be having
back-to-back funerals.
They brought it on themselves.
[hums thoughtfully]
This is why I like you.
Because you don't waste sympathy.
[♪ suspenseful music crescendos]
Shall we end our meeting here?
-Good work.
-[all] Nice work, everyone.
Ms. Yoo.
Can we talk separately?
What is it?
[♪ upbeat pop music playing]
Someone might see us.
You shouldn't be so pretty then.
From now on,
don't show up too pretty
when you come for the meetings.
I can't concentrate.
[chuckles softly]
Stop texting me during the meetings.
I'm nervous we'll be caught.
[Wonseok] We made sure it clearly conveys
a sense of premium and gift value.
Next, the product features
a single material
that's water-based and plant-derived...
[Kim Wooju] Why are you so pretty today?
[Wonseok] ...with enhanced
eco-friendly standards.
We used internal QR printing
and personalization
to transform the unboxing
into a storytelling journey.
The next challenge we needed to address
-was that the previous packaging...
-[phone vibrates]
...had its limits
in terms of luxury and finish,
which made it somewhat
inconsistent as a gift set.
[Kim Wooju] Let's have lunch together
after this.
Just the two of us.
[Wonseok] It was also difficult
to reflect the campaign message.
We also received feedback
that the excessive packaging
lessened the eco-friendly impression.
So, why didn't you reply to them?
How could I?
Songhee and Sejung were sitting around me.
And you're saved
as "Team Leader Kim Wooju,"
so they'd know straight away.
Then change the contact name.
Change it to Myungsik.
And you can be Myungsoon.
Sounds great, right?
[both giggle]
What are you doing the day after?
[sighs wearily]
[Ms. Oh] Attention, please.
Attention.
-[Wonseok clears throat]
-Chairwoman Ko asked our team...
-[mouthing]
-[sighs softly]
...to come visit her house!
[chuckles]
Oh, you!
She invites each department
about once every other year.
She has lunch with our head office staff
and partner companies,
encourages them,
and listens to their concerns.
It's our tradition.
Wow, the chairwoman is really amazing.
She also invites the partner companies?
Of course.
She does if they're important companies.
She invited us, too?
Yes.
Why? Are you nervous?
I'm not sure
if it's appropriate for us to join.
Of course, it is.
Grandma loved your designs.
She invited you to thank you personally.
[chuckles softly] Don't worry too much.
[inhales deeply, hums thoughtfully]
Just think of it as a quick preview.
Okay, then.
And don't show up looking too pretty.
[chuckles softly]
[♪ whimsical sting]
Seriously, someone will see us.
Who cares?
It's our company.
[both giggle]
-Well, my grandmother's company.
-[Meri chuckles]
[both chuckle]
What should we eat
to celebrate his discharge?
Wooju is the one
being discharged, not you.
What would you like to eat, Wooju?
You two eat.
I have somewhere to be.
[Wooju's sister exclaims]
MYUNGSOONDANG
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
[wind blowing]
Team leader of the marketing team.
I'm going to get you fired.
TEAM LEADER KIM WOOJU'S POWER ABUSE REPORT
There's something I need
to report to the chairwoman.
I said, no.
I'll just pass her this.
Seriously, you can't.
Please!
[Wooju grunts, exclaims]
Why are you doing this?
I just need a moment.
Seriously, stop this!
[gate closes]
[♪ gripping, dramatic music playing]
[sighs]
I will still get in.
[♪ dramatic sting]
That's a separate promotion,
so we've set aside
a separate budget for it.
Yes.
Mr. Kim Wooju confirmed it.
Okay.
-[line disconnects]
-[sighs] He's all over me.
-Is it Mr. Jang Eungsoo?
-Yes.
As the previous team leader,
he should know our situation.
Why is he being so nitpicky?
[Sejung] It's because
it's Mr. Kim's project.
According to Mr. Han,
it's really fierce between them right now.
Between them?
With Mr. Kim?
-Between paternal and maternal grandsons?
-Yes.
But isn't it obvious
that Mr. Kim would be the next successor?
I think Mr. Jang is the only one
who thinks this is a competition.
-[whispers] Be quiet.
-[elevator chimes]
[elevator doors open]
[whispering indistinctly]
[elevator chimes]
[speaking indistinctly]
[♪ dramatic guitar music playing]
Paternal grandson?
Successor of Myungsoondang?
MYUNGSOONDANG CHAIRWOMAN KO
WINS THE PRESIDENT'S AWARD
Fourth-generation successor
of Myungsoondang.
This is all useless.
I EXPOSE THE POWER ABUSE
OF MARKETING TEAM LEADER, KIM WOOJU!
[Wooju singing]
♪ Like being shot ♪
[♪ somber pop music playing]
♪ I can't even think straight ♪
♪ All I could do was laugh ♪
♪ So I just laughed ♪
[breath trembling]
♪ I did ♪
♪ With that hollow laugh ♪
♪ I only wanted to ask one thing ♪
♪ Why are we breaking up? ♪
♪ How can we break up? ♪
♪ How can we? ♪
♪ Through the hole in my chest ♪
♪ Our memories keep spilling out ♪
[sobbing]
♪ I try to hold them in ♪
♪ I press against my heart ♪
♪ But they slip away through my fingers ♪
It's nice, right?
But is Mr. Kim not coming?
I'm sure he's inside.
Mr. Kim is the chairwoman's grandson.
-[whispers] What?
-Yes.
Really?
Hurry up.
[Sejung] Okay.
Excuse me.
[Wonseok clears throat]
It's a really nice house, right?
Yes, it is.
[Wonseok chuckles]
-It's your first time here, right?
-[Sejung] It's really nice.
Their ceiling is so high, don't you think?
I'm so jealous.
I want to live in a house like this.
[Songhee] That lamp is really expensive.
-[Sejung] Which one?
-[Songhee] That one.
-[Sejung] That one?
-[Wonseok] Yes.
[Philnyun] Welcome.
Thank you for coming.
Have a sit.
[Kim Wooju sighs]
Chairwoman, thank you for inviting us.
I meant to invite
the marketing team sooner,
but it took longer than planned.
[Philnyun chuckles]
They're from Merry Design Studio.
This is the CEO, Ms. Yoo Meri,
and this is Ms. Shin Songhee.
-Hello, ma'am.
-Nice to meet you.
[chuckles softly]
I did hear the Myungsoon, Myungsik project
got a good response.
Mr. Kim praised you a lot,
saying that our online sales increased
thanks to the skilled partner company.
[chuckles softly] Thank you.
[chuckles softly]
Thank you for your kind words.
[♪ gripping, whimsical music playing]
[Juhee] Shall I get lunch ready?
Oh, my. Look at me.
You all must be hungry.
-Let's eat. [chuckles softly]
-[all acknowledging]
[♪ ethereal sparkle]
-Thank you.
-[Sejung] Thank you.
It's nothing fancy, but please enjoy.
-[Ms. Oh] Thank you for the food.
-[Wonseok] Thank you.
[Ms. Oh] Ma'am,
did you make
the dumplings yourself again today?
Yes, why? Does it taste weird?
Not at all.
Dumplings remind me of you now.
Do you remember?
About 9 or 10 years ago,
we made a thousand dumplings
at an orphanage.
[gasps softly]
What do you mean?
Every year during the holidays,
there's an orphanage
that our company visits.
It's our annual event to go there
and make dumplings to eat together.
We make a large batch
so they can freeze some for later.
But because it's a lot of work,
I was going to make a few by hand
and buy the rest from a shop.
But I got caught.
[all chuckle]
Of all days,
the chairwoman herself came that day.
I was scolded a lot.
And that whole day,
we made a thousand dumplings
with Chairwoman.
[Songhee gasps]
You have slow hands.
I think the others, Ms. Kim,
and I made most of them.
Still, they were delicious.
In cooking, sincerity is everything.
So, you've got to be honest
from the start.
Even if they're children,
you can't lie to them,
saying they're hand-made
when they're store-bought.
Once you start lying,
it's easy to lie again.
A one-time cheater can easily turn
into a career criminal.
Maybe it's because
I'm in the food business,
but I hate deceiving people
more than anything.
Especially if it's for their own gain,
I don't even associate with them.
That's my one solid principle.
[Ms. Oh] Of course, I know.
[♪ poignant, melancholy music playing]
[Wonseok] That was a great meal.
[Sejung] I'm so full.
-That was delicious, right?
-[Wonseok] Yes, it was.
-[Ms. Oh] It was delicious. Thank you.
-[all] Thank you.
Thank you for enjoying them.
Stay with us for a long time
to come visit again.
-Of course!
-[Philnyun chuckles softly]
Mr. Kim, are you going to the office?
I'm going straight to an external meeting.
Okay, then.
-You should all get going.
-[all] Okay.
-[all] Goodbye.
-[Ms. Oh] We'll get going then.
[Jingyeong] Grandma!
Hi, Jingyeong.
[♪ soft, melancholy music playing]
You have guests.
They were just about to leave.
Let's go in.
Okay.
-Did you eat?
-No, I'm so hungry.
-Were you too busy to eat?
-Yes.
What would you like, Jingyeong?
-I like anything that you make.
-[chuckles]
Let's go in.
I'll make you something delicious.
[Jingyeong] Okay.
I had no idea.
You could've told me sooner.
You didn't know?
Fair enough.
You can be a bit clueless sometimes.
[scoffs]
[Ms. Oh] What about you, Ms. Yoo?
You knew, right?
[Songhee chuckles softly]
Pardon?
That Mr. Kim is the chairwoman's grandson.
Oh, I recently found out.
[Ms. Oh] You know, you lined up well.
So, step up, okay?
Mr. Kim will soon own the company.
Sure.
Mr. Han.
That woman before...
Doesn't she seem like the one
in the marriage talks with Mr. Kim?
[Wonseok inhales deeply] I'm not sure.
She does seem like the one.
What's this about?
[chuckles, inhales deeply]
Are you curious?
Tell me now.
It's about Mr. Kim.
They say there's
a marriage talk between him
and the chairwoman's doctor's daughter.
[Ms. Oh] Really?
Why are you telling me this now?
Because you didn't ask.
-You startled me.
-[Ms. Oh] Seriously.
I should've gotten a closer look at her.
She was pretty.
[Wonseok] She's the hospital director's
daughter, and she's a doctor herself.
Apparently, the chairwoman
really dotes on her.
-[Ms. Oh] Really?
-[Wonseok] Yes.
[Ms. Oh gasps] How did I not know this?
[machine beeping]
I wouldn't have called if I'd known
Director Yoon was away at the conference.
Sorry to bother you.
It's nothing.
My father specifically told me
to take good care of you.
Are you uncomfortable anywhere else?
[hums thoughtfully]
I'm not getting good sleep.
I keep dreaming about my late husband.
It's really disturbing.
Grandma, I think
that's a lottery-winning dream.
I bet he was trying to tell you
the winning number.
You shouldn't have woken up.
-What a shame.
-[chuckling]
What's the point of making more money?
It's not like I'm going
to take it to my grave.
I'll be satisfied if I can see Wooju
get married before I go.
Are things going well with Wooju?
-[hesitates]
-What is it?
It's not going well?
They say there's no tree
that won't fall after ten swings.
[♪ melancholy music playing]
Grandma,
I've been thinking.
I think I like Wooju more
as a brother than as a boyfriend.
[sighs wearily]
[realtor] Hello, everyone!
Today, I'm here at Beauté Palace.
The pre-sale price here
used to be under three million dollars,
but recently, prices have hit the roof.
So, the latest deals are
at least five million dollars.
[gasps in awe]
Oh, and apparently,
Beauté Department Store
even gave away one of these units
as a prize for newlyweds.
Five million dollars?
-But honestly, that's just a dream
-Really?
for people like us.
I understand
if it's for five million dollars.
[realtor] But as you can see here,
it's decorated with flowers
and a European touch...
Are you just going to stay home?
Aren't you going to get a job?
[sighs in exasperation]
[Eunsook sighs]
This is a medical report
from the hospital.
Send it to the insurance.
[Wooju whining] The insurance payout
isn't even that much!
I put you down for a lot of them.
For the ones I paid for, bring them to me.
Fine!
I'll get the insurance payout.
You can keep them all!
[mumbles]
Where are you going?
You broke off the engagement.
Why are you taking it out on me?
Mom, try to be more understanding.
He's having a complete mental breakdown.
He got dumped by Jenny.
Meri got herself a boyfriend.
[tsk-tsk]
I bet it stings even more
because he trusted her.
Meri really has no principles, does she?
It hasn't even been that long.
I've been thinking about it,
and I think when she came to our house,
she was already seeing someone else.
She was that confident
because she had someone to fall back on.
I'm going to see
just how great this guy she's dating is.
He seemed great.
You've got to admit,
Meri has good luck with guys, right?
She does not.
Where are you going?
With Wooju like that,
I should at least snag myself a man.
Ms. Chun.
I'm going to be home late. [giggles]
Hey.
You look pretty today.
Yes.
I've submitted the report
through the internet.
How much is the payout?
Really?
It's coming into my account, right?
[chuckles]
Okay, noted.
Thank you.
-[line disconnects]
-It's a lot more than I thought.
[slaps table, sighs thoughtfully]
If I had known,
I would've put myself down for more.
Wait a minute.
Didn't Meri sign me up for some insurance?
Which company was it?
INSURANCE
What?
The insurance beneficiary is Yoo Meri?
[adjuster] Yes, the insured is listed
as Mr. Kim Wooju,
but both the policyholder
and the beneficiary
are registered as Ms. Yoo Meri.
Why would she...
1 YEAR AGO
Here.
[♪ gripping music playing]
What's this?
CERTIFICATE OF INSURANCE
I signed you up for your insurance
when I did mine.
Once you get a job, you can pay for it.
And change the beneficiary then.
COMPREHENSIVE ACCIDENT
INSURANCE POLICY TERMS
[scoffs]
She put herself down as the beneficiary
because she's paying for it.
[clears throat]
But we're no longer together
because we're divorced.
So, I need to change the beneficiary.
[adjuster] Oh, is that so?
In that case,
submit your marriage certificate
with the divorce date indicated.
Then you can change the beneficiary.
Okay, got it.
-[line disconnects]
-[sighs wearily] How bothersome.
What the heck? Seriously?
[♪ poignant music playing]
[Philnyun] But I hate deceiving people
more than anything.
Especially if it's for their own gain,
I don't even associate with them.
That's my one solid principle.
-Were you too busy to eat?
-Yes.
What would you like, Jingyeong?
[Jingyeong] I like anything that you make.
[Philnyun chuckles] Let's see.
What would you find delicious?
MYUNGSOON
MYUNGSIK
Hello?
I'm eating right now.
Right now?
Yes.
I was just heading home
after my meeting nearby.
I'll come to you.
Okay, then.
[line disconnects]
[gasps] I should get changed.
[cutlery, dishes clatter]
[doorbell chimes]
[exclaims quizzically]
Is he here already?
-[door keypad beeps]
-You got here so fast.
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
Waiting for someone?
I have nothing to say to you.
I told you I'm done with you.
I'm reporting you
to the police for stalking.
I should be the one reporting you.
[scoffs]
PROOF OF MARRIAGE
Did you have fun so far?
The fake newlywed life.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ ethereal sparkle]
[♪ sentimental pop music playing]
WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
[Wooju] So, end it unless you want
to see him go down!
[Meri] I did as you asked.
So, don't do anything to him.
He's got nothing to do with me now.
[Wooju] I'll make you pay if you call
the police. I'll make Kim Wooju pay, too.
-Leave him alone!
-Why, you...
[Kim Wooju] Even if it's just for a day,
I want to be with you.
So, stay by my side.
Grandma's been really curious about you.
Mr. Baek is on his way here.
[Philnyun] Are you personally close
to my Wooju?
[Sanghyeon] What's your relationship
with Ms. Yoo?
Are you two really married?
Translated by Susanna Kim